<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Color Out of Space[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5073642</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Color Out of Space</title>
	<year>2020</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Gardner family moves to a remote farmstead in rural New England to escape the hustle of the 21st century. They are busy adapting to their new life when a meteorite crashes into their front yard, melts into the earth, and infects both the land and the properties of space-time with a strange, otherworldly colour. To their horror, the family discovers this alien force is gradually mutating every life form that it touches—including them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vkwgzCBBiY3C1XEy0WakYfMOvnG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iyn2JQsftaqhQlXYaCCvn8udM5i.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Annihilation[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2798920</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Annihilation</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A biologist signs up for a dangerous, secret expedition into a mysterious zone where the laws of nature don't apply.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/d3qcpfNwbAMCNqWDHzPQsUYiUgS.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5zfVNTrkhMu673zma6qhFzG01ig.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Arrival[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2543164</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Arrival</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Taking place after alien crafts land around the world, an expert linguist is recruited by the military to determine whether they come in peace or are a threat.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x2FJsf1ElAgr63Y3PNPtJrcmpoe.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hNCqkXbWd40eftqSdjq8TmV7Mqr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Edge of Tomorrow[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1631867</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Edge of Tomorrow</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Major Bill Cage is an officer who has never seen a day of combat when he is unceremoniously demoted and dropped into combat. Cage is killed within minutes, managing to take an alpha alien down with him. He awakens back at the beginning of the same day and is forced to fight and die again... and again - as physical contact with the alien has thrown him into a time loop.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uUHvlkLavotfGsNtosDy8ShsIYF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/auZIuHEUec5tBTns3tCRXfayxZq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Oblivion[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1483013</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Oblivion</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Jack Harper is one of the last few drone repairmen stationed on Earth.  Part of a massive operation to extract vital resources after decades of war with a terrifying threat known as the Scavs, Jack’s mission is nearly complete.  His existence is brought crashing down when he rescues a beautiful  stranger from a downed spacecraft.  Her arrival triggers a chain of events that  forces him to question everything he knows and puts the fate of humanity in his hands.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2ncs7hqBsEjFMqt6Y7ShBCO9tWs.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Pv6vu1lxgct3GWhUXVVOMZwNlZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Cloverfield[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1060277</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Cloverfield</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Five young New Yorkers throw their friend a going-away party the night that a monster the size of a skyscraper descends upon the city. Told from the point of view of their video camera, the film is a document of their attempt to survive the most surreal, horrifying event of their lives.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qIegUGJqyMMCRjkKV1s7A9MqdJ8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4bFj3pUdFCO6tbOkNTCzAWncJU8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]10 Cloverfield Lane[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1179933</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>10 Cloverfield Lane</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After getting in a car accident, a woman is held in a shelter with two men, who claim the outside world is affected by a widespread chemical attack.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/84Dhwz93vCin6T1PX6ctSvWEuNE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9G8SmOBWuo0ME6FIwCockkwbNMq.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Signs[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0286106</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Signs</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A family living on a farm finds mysterious crop circles in their fields which suggests something more frightening to come.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hyZkNEbNgnciUVTyu4NZTjlCh4L.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aMiI1j9L8V1EBL0CNZaekQC9AW3.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Life[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5442430</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Life</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The six-member crew of the International Space Station is tasked with studying a sample from Mars that may be the first proof of extra-terrestrial life, which proves more intelligent than ever expected.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lja0Kh17LLleh6DhtixEh7Z7T6D.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nNh7vHHISVAaziJEqAq0P9iL52w.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]War of the Worlds[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0407304</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>War of the Worlds</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Ray Ferrier is a divorced dockworker and less-than-perfect father. Soon after his ex-wife and her new husband drop off his teenage son and young daughter for a rare weekend visit, a strange and powerful lightning storm touches down.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6Biy7R9LfumYshur3YKhpj56MpB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nH6hPhJq3EEv9CnBZgXU3IQnpJo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Pacific Rim[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1663662</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pacific Rim</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When legions of monstrous creatures, known as Kaiju, started rising from the sea, a war began that would take millions of lives and consume humanity's resources for years on end. To combat the giant Kaiju, a special type of weapon was devised: massive robots, called Jaegers, which are controlled simultaneously by two pilots whose minds are locked in a neural bridge. But even the Jaegers are proving nearly defenseless in the face of the relentless Kaiju. On the verge of defeat, the forces defending mankind have no choice but to turn to two unlikely heroes—a washed-up former pilot (Charlie Hunnam) and an untested trainee (Rinko Kikuchi)—who are teamed to drive a legendary but seemingly obsolete Jaeger from the past. Together, they stand as mankind's last hope against the mounting apocalypse.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mmznhaQDwlHWpUwKuNxtQiubbmM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ig7qUy7drkEFZNCK7gi0hMn1WMN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]District 9[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1136608</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>District 9</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Thirty years ago, aliens arrive on Earth. Not to conquer or give aid, but to find refuge from their dying planet. Separated from humans in a South African area called District 9, the aliens are managed by Multi-National United, which is unconcerned with the aliens' welfare but will do anything to master their advanced technology. When a company field agent contracts a mysterious virus that begins to alter his DNA, there is only one place he can hide: District 9.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tuGlQkqLxnodDSk6mp5c2wvxUEd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vR5aTnCCnBrHY33E4robIUmJ4nN.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]A Quiet Place[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6644200</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Quiet Place</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A family is forced to live in silence while hiding from creatures that hunt by sound.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nAU74GmpUk7t5iklEp3bufwDq4n.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/roYyPiQDQKmIKUEhO912693tSja.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The 5th Wave[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2304933</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The 5th Wave</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>16-year-old Cassie Sullivan tries to survive in a world devastated by the waves of an alien invasion that has already decimated the population and knocked mankind back to the Stone Age.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4Dd79cz5qxKNoKWg1xsfrpOchEr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iaLu7WlCaK3jy2wz0uDcqiJxCd9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Thing[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0084787</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Thing</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Members of an American scientific research outpost in Antarctica find themselves battling a parasitic alien organism capable of perfectly imitating its victims. They soon discover that this task will be harder than they thought, as they don't know which members of the team have already been assimilated and their paranoia threatens to tear them apart.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tzGY49kseSE9QAKk47uuDGwnSCu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lS9oEknIMaNvIm2zpXg5MXDDmZx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Fire in the Sky[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fire in the Sky</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A group of men who were clearing bush for the government arrive back in town, claiming that their friend was abducted by aliens. Nobody believes them, and despite a lack of motive and no evidence of foul play, their friends' disappearance is treated as murder.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6Q2cjuMuqticomBjmwxwu8tyWEP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vgPw7NfqAF0kK2UMuUG7t0oRLS1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083866</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After a gentle alien becomes stranded on Earth, the being is discovered and befriended by a young boy named Elliott. Bringing the extraterrestrial into his suburban California house, Elliott introduces E.T., as the alien is dubbed, to his brother and his little sister, Gertie, and the children decide to keep its existence a secret. Soon, however, E.T. falls ill, resulting in government intervention and a dire situation for both Elliott and the alien.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pEKStszBzTZCvR0H4tosjqxmE7X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mXLVA0YL6tcXi6SJSuAh9ONXFj5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Avatar[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0499549</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Avatar</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the 22nd century, a paraplegic Marine is dispatched to the moon Pandora on a unique mission, but becomes torn between following orders and protecting an alien civilization.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6EiRUJpuoeQPghrs3YNktfnqOVh.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bIL7ENqh1egWTxN41sM2W42JqPc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Contact[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0118884</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Contact</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Contact is a science fiction film about an encounter with alien intelligence. Based on the novel by Carl Sagan the film starred Jodie Foster as the one chosen scientist who must make some difficult decisions between her beliefs, the truth, and reality.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bCpMIywuNZeWt3i5UMLEIc0VSwM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x5Z2BjuUfEEwYWZccDwbU9KSEqj.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Day the Earth Stood Still[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0970416</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Day the Earth Stood Still</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A representative of an alien race that went through drastic evolution to survive its own climate change, Klaatu comes to Earth to assess whether humanity can prevent the environmental damage they have inflicted on their own planet. When barred from speaking to the United Nations, he decides humankind shall be exterminated so the planet can survive.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mrw9NShY6I2FgXwk8Ge437pn08N.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iejDBhNCQwvzp1IuTmOY9L2VZsK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Men in Black[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119654</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Men in Black</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After a police chase with an otherworldly being, a New York City cop is recruited as an agent in a top-secret organization established to monitor and police alien activity on Earth: the Men in Black. Agent Kay and new recruit Agent Jay find themselves in the middle of a deadly plot by an intergalactic terrorist who has arrived on Earth to assassinate two ambassadors from opposing galaxies.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uLOmOF5IzWoyrgIF5MfUnh5pa1X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1GJvBE7UWU1WOVi0XREl4JQc7f8.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Men in Black II[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120912</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Men in Black II</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Kay and Jay reunite to provide our best, last and only line of defense against a sinister seductress who levels the toughest challenge yet to the MIB's untarnished mission statement – protecting Earth from the scum of the universe. It's been four years since the alien-seeking agents averted an intergalactic disaster of epic proportions. Now it's a race against the clock as Jay must convince Kay – who not only has absolutely no memory of his time spent with the MIB, but is also the only living person left with the expertise to save the galaxy – to reunite with the MIB before the earth submits to ultimate destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/enA22EPyzc2WQ1VVyY7zxresQQr.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4jQHLKqVpvWoW8letxMwiN02ySI.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Men in Black 3[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1409024</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Men in Black 3</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Agents J and K are back...in time. J has seen some inexplicable things in his 15 years with the Men in Black, but nothing, not even aliens, perplexes him as much as his wry, reticent partner. But when K's life and the fate of the planet are put at stake, Agent J will have to travel back in time to put things right. J discovers that there are secrets to the universe that K never told him - secrets that will reveal themselves as he teams up with the young Agent K to save his partner, the agency, and the future of humankind.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e7kebbtwqzqam6l11aQNl7lXMs0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/44mAbdjGrJJQ4hzkKx2Z2EsninZ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Captive State[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5968394</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Captive State</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Nearly a decade after occupation by an extraterrestrial force, the lives of a Chicago neighborhood on both sides of the conflict are explored. In a working-class Chicago neighborhood occupied by an alien force for nine years, increased surveillance and the restriction of civil rights have given rise to an authoritarian system -- and dissent among the populace.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cVo7lylXAUDGuvDZBUYaP8Zjbku.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6IZ84KFhNpy6htsJmwFVuK30pyp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Fourth Kind[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1220198</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fourth Kind</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Since the 1960s, a disproportionate number of the population in and around Nome, Alaska, have gone missing. Despite FBI investigations, the disappearances remain a mystery. Dr. Abigail Tyler, a psychologist, may be on the verge of blowing the unsolved cases wide open when, during the course of treating her patients, she finds evidence of alien abductions.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vfnsGUwurUQqlpvArBvUVc9rYXa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q7C7PM6ldX8gdMDP8WGnvLt6KLX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Invasion[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0427392</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Invasion</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Washington, D.C. psychologist Carol Bennell and her colleague Dr. Ben Driscoll are the only two people on Earth who are aware of an epidemic running rampant through the city. They discover an alien virus aboard a crashed space shuttle that transforms anyone who comes into contact with it into unfeeling drones while they sleep. Carol realizes her son holds the key to stopping the spread of the plague and she races to find him before it is too late.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/69yA6E7JOKJSfK8JMAOsieCDB8A.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/i2qe6LRYUbYIITw5vSH6UlBMrRS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Independence Day[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116629</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Independence Day</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>On July 2, a giant alien mothership enters orbit around Earth and deploys several dozen saucer-shaped 'destroyer' spacecraft that quickly lay waste to major cities around the planet. On July 3, the United States conducts a coordinated counterattack that fails. On July 4, a plan is devised to gain access to the interior of the alien mothership in space, in order to plant a nuclear missile.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/p0BPQGSPoSa8Ml0DAf2mB2kCU0R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uw4SnKFZ453Gxmj5XR5Susj8TNo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Arrival[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0115571</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Arrival</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Zane Ziminski is an astrophysicist who receives a message that seems to have extraterrestrial origins. Eerily soon after his discovery, Zane is fired. He then embarks on a search to determine the origins of the transmission that leads him into a Hitchcockian labyrinth of paranoia and intrigue.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/srPCUXcw6vEZWQBeN7hDd6DiETg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oJ597dVjLMICx56clM7iy3AUUsA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Zathura: A Space Adventure[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0406375</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Zathura: A Space Adventure</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After their father is called into work, two young boys, Walter and Danny, are left in the care of their teenage sister, Lisa, and told they must stay inside. Walter and Danny, who anticipate a boring day, are shocked when they begin playing Zathura, a space-themed board game, which they realize has mystical powers when their house is shot into space. With the help of an astronaut, the boys attempt to return home.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/s3uFIwMYiSmsYGj2wfFGCdogOLE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2DKpjWI0j6eRhF3lPUE4lc7wqP0.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Species[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0114508</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Species</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1993, the Search for Extra Terrestrial Intelligence Project receives a transmission detailing an alien DNA structure, along with instructions on how to splice it with human DNA. The result is Sil, a sensual but deadly creature who can change from a beautiful woman to an armour-plated killing machine in the blink of an eye.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wxddZZM4LzlCMVcC4Bdiborh7Jf.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bTHqaM1SVXSpEELkZ471MFlt53s.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Independence Day: Resurgence[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1628841</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Independence Day: Resurgence</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>We always knew they were coming back. Using recovered alien technology, the nations of Earth have collaborated on an immense defense program to protect the planet. But nothing can prepare us for the aliens’ advanced and unprecedented force. Only the ingenuity of a few brave men and women can bring our world back from the brink of extinction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jzpvh0Ic7jL9GX4NLE1Tx2GUCrN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ou70x2658dVnbycIRaC37sEeafS.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]2001: A Space Odyssey[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0062622</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>2001: A Space Odyssey</title>
	<year>1968</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Humanity finds a mysterious object buried beneath the lunar surface and sets off to find its origins with the help of HAL 9000, the world's most advanced super computer.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zmmYdPa8Lxx999Af9vnVP4XQ1V6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/spoZUN4X1KiOc5S0plOyGAXLNtb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Close Encounters of the Third Kind[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0075860</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Close Encounters of the Third Kind</title>
	<year>1977</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After an encounter with UFOs, a line worker feels undeniably drawn to an isolated area in the wilderness where something spectacular is about to happen.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kzD5ng3BvRUxW9vBfCkg61XjITR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iYtvvkuBo6pxLdoIqZZxN97vDzW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Invasion of the Body Snatchers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0077745</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Invasion of the Body Snatchers</title>
	<year>1978</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The first remake of the paranoid infiltration classic moves the setting for the invasion, from a small town to the city of San Francisco and starts as Matthew Bennell notices that several of his friends are complaining that their close relatives are in some way different. When questioned later they themselves seem changed, as they deny everything or make lame excuses. As the invaders increase in number they become more open and Bennell, who has by now witnessed an attempted "replacement", realises that he and his friends must escape or suffer the same fate. But who can he trust to help him and who has already been snatched?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/skS02wdeH2C0nrbCQP3qKwJdZtZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/psAYbe3Jjb5nxeGOsk5oSeFJ5tK.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Fifth Element[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119116</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Fifth Element</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 2257, a taxi driver is unintentionally given the task of saving a young girl who is part of the key that will ensure the survival of humanity.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fPtlCO1yQtnoLHOwKtWz7db6RGU.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fuiKROO8Xm0LbGnekpR6nv4eC2Y.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Predator[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0093773</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Predator</title>
	<year>1987</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Dutch and his group of commandos are hired by the CIA to rescue downed airmen from guerillas in a Central American jungle. The mission goes well but as they return they find that something is hunting them. Nearly invisible, it blends in with the forest, taking trophies from the bodies of its victims as it goes along. Occasionally seeing through its eyes, the audience sees it is an intelligent alien hunter, hunting them for sport, killing them off one at a time.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qBvKSCBnGhqCHhRUMXcJE4qz7vc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2k9RDzmUpd68zXDsEBN0lYx7Zmv.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Total Recall[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0100802</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Total Recall</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Construction worker Douglas Quaid discovers a memory chip in his brain during a virtual-reality trip. He also finds that his past has been invented to conceal a plot of planetary domination. Soon, he's off to Mars to find out who he is and who planted the chip.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wVbeL6fkbTKSmNfalj4VoAUUqJv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/axFOnFEfsG0Z1pdiUZZhfi8vsR5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Star Trek[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0796366</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Star Trek</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The fate of the galaxy rests in the hands of bitter rivals. One, James Kirk, is a delinquent, thrill-seeking Iowa farm boy. The other, Spock, a Vulcan, was raised in a logic-based society that rejects all emotion. As fiery instinct clashes with calm reason, their unlikely but powerful partnership is the only thing capable of leading their crew through unimaginable danger, boldly going where no one has gone before. The human adventure has begun again.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hN2ZtF3Uw6mhIHZiqL0SKzELtKn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zzzoRNVSaUv6e1hpADjUDeM3EvY.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Pitch Black[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0134847</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Pitch Black</title>
	<year>2000</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When their ship crash-lands on a remote planet, the marooned passengers soon learn that escaped convict Riddick isn't the only thing they have to fear. Deadly creatures lurk in the shadows, waiting to attack in the dark, and the planet is rapidly plunging into the utter blackness of a total eclipse. With the body count rising, the doomed survivors are forced to turn to Riddick with his eerie eyes to guide them through the darkness to safety. With time running out, there's only one rule: Stay in the light.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5F1sINO5CGUh9tK6eGg8mRCPhQM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jIibfKqDN5i5ZU0vshk06UEUaVg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Abyss[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096754</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Abyss</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A civilian oil rig crew is recruited to conduct a search and rescue effort when a nuclear submarine mysteriously sinks. One diver soon finds himself on a spectacular odyssey 25,000 feet below the ocean's surface where he confronts a mysterious force that has the power to change the world or destroy it.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jel2BuDv7Bq4fuv2pUrTfiBm69o.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aPB3jFuMSoNFk2uDZ5tX5CIGaSX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Starship Troopers[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120201</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Starship Troopers</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Set in the future, the story follows a young soldier named Johnny Rico and his exploits in the Mobile Infantry. Rico's military career progresses from recruit to non-commissioned officer and finally to officer against the backdrop of an interstellar war between mankind and an arachnoid species known as "the Bugs".</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/cxCmv23O7p3hyHwqoktHYkZcGsY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h3WZqzEBWmHYC7DCQ5aidnbV5oe.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0371724</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mere seconds before the Earth is to be demolished by an alien construction crew, Arthur Dent is swept off the planet by his friend Ford Prefect, a researcher penning a new edition of "The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy."</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tcrkbs4ezEklmvt39b01881P6CN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7wr3TRFpeTqotoU9FlHb5DeFQ4K.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Stargate[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0111282</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Stargate</title>
	<year>1994</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>An interstellar teleportation device, found in Egypt, leads to a planet with humans resembling ancient Egyptians who worship the god Ra.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fyTqTETiXncfESLyKfkgEs7qg7d.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tcbghgBjTO3qHTEhB1ISdd59biL.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Alien[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0078748</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien</title>
	<year>1979</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>During its return to the earth, commercial spaceship Nostromo intercepts a distress signal from a distant planet. When a three-member team of the crew discovers a chamber containing thousands of eggs on the planet, a creature inside one of the eggs attacks an explorer. The entire crew is unaware of the impending nightmare set to descend upon them when the alien parasite planted inside its unfortunate host is birthed.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vfrQk5IPloGg1v9Rzbh2Eg3VGyM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AmR3JG1VQVxU8TfAvljUhfSFUOx.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Aliens[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090605</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Aliens</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Ripley's lifepod is found by a salvage crew over 50 years later, she finds that terra-formers are on the very planet they found the alien species. When the company sends a family of colonists out to investigate her story—all contact is lost with the planet and colonists. They enlist Ripley and the colonial marines to return and search for answers.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7lh0lceTCEatJlsmiwkun5AC4OV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/jMBpJFRtrtIXymer93XLavPwI3P.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Alien³[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103644</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien³</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After escaping with Newt and Hicks from the alien planet, Ripley crash lands on Fiorina 161, a prison planet and host to a correctional facility. Unfortunately, although Newt and Hicks do not survive the crash, a more unwelcome visitor does. The prison does not allow weapons of any kind, and with aid being a long time away, the prisoners must simply survive in any way they can.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hlabk6APJUeihZDaSD9N6iI0f4g.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9WO0CELoWq6tSdjqCs34Y0qek7l.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Alien: Covenant[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2316204</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Alien: Covenant</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Bound for a remote planet on the far side of the galaxy, the crew of the colony ship 'Covenant' discovers what is thought to be an uncharted paradise, but is actually a dark, dangerous world—which has a sole inhabitant: the 'synthetic', David, survivor of the doomed Prometheus expedition.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zecMELPbU5YMQpC81Z8ImaaXuf9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6jajFcaY2YsfGQstJ5HaqZNVseX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Prometheus[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1446714</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Prometheus</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A team of explorers discover a clue to the origins of mankind on Earth, leading them on a journey to the darkest corners of the universe. There, they must fight a terrifying battle to save the future of the human race.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/omy5CiDMQnGqQUEJ9gNLOGPZQFW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bgc28hV0Rxkw4RqtxzjsfY4vfqO.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The X Files[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120902</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The X Files</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mulder and Scully, now taken off the FBI's X Files cases, must find a way to fight the shadowy elements of the government to find out the truth about a conspiracy that might mean the alien colonization of Earth.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yLIw6shz2WC3W3iI0jROsF4B2ha.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2ZuNdBOSUamCo6mU1Ew1KEaN8Zc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Galaxy Quest[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0177789</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Galaxy Quest</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The stars of a 1980s sci-fi show—now eking out a living through re-runs and sci-fi conventions—are beamed aboard an alien spacecraft. Believing the cast's heroic on-screen dramas are historical documents of real-life adventures, the band of aliens turn to the cast members for help in their quest to overcome the oppressive regime in their solar system.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fZXSwgZknp81vmciTb86rw0MejV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/olWRQUJhBTD5GR1SNNIMJYDG6ka.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Mars Attacks![/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116996</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mars Attacks!</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>'We come in peace' is not what those green men from Mars mean when they invade our planet, armed with irresistible weapons and a cruel sense of humor.  This star studded cast must play victim to the alien’s fun and games in this comedy homage to science fiction films of the '50s and '60s.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hll4O5vSAfnZDb6JbnP06GPtz7b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4qFcUKlkcUj9V9Cbh1tyyLmg2rE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]They Live[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096256</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>They Live</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Nada, a wanderer without meaning in his life, discovers a pair of sunglasses capable of showing the world the way it truly is. As he walks the streets of Los Angeles, Nada notices that both the media and the government are comprised of subliminal messages meant to keep the population subdued, and that most of the social elite are skull-faced aliens bent on world domination. With this shocking discovery, Nada fights to free humanity from the mind-controlling aliens.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ngnybFTuopfbfmmEeX9jjBQQmF6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3k2DQBryXzaL7DoAtu6veWWluwt.jpg</fanart>
</item>
