<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Haunted Mansion[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0338094</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Haunted Mansion</title>
	<year>2003</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Workaholic Jim Evers and his wife/business partner Sara get a call one night from  a mansion owner, Edward Gracey, who wants to sell his house. Once the Evers family arrive at the mansion, a torrential thunderstorm of mysterious origin strands them with the brooding, eccentric Gracey, his mysterious butler, and a variety of residents both seen and unseen.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lGi5yio4pdDz5PkSeZCbnMQz5vK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ardDe5n33i0061Au5qNZaWiEPJg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Tower of Terror[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0131620</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Tower of Terror</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A disgraced reporter investigates an abandoned luxury hotel where five people mysteriously disappeared sixty years earlier.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4AUcvFKrP4ke8pTTAvkS6OHuDqn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/logfMF9jvC1qq9Y3pgOneFs74nr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Race to Witch Mountain[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1075417</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Race to Witch Mountain</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A taxi driver gets more than he bargained for when he picks up two teen runaways. Not only does the pair possess supernatural powers, but they're also trying desperately to escape people who have made them their targets.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9kFqOiQg1VtBKelhappX9iGQDAw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eJJ7pFCQOL8kvjsoFD3V7CAqL0d.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Scream Team[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0313634</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Scream Team</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Eccentric Frank Carlyle ran a horror shop in small-town Steeple Falls, which takes pride in and profit from its Halloween traditions. Frank's widower grandson Richard grudgingly returns there from Boston with his own kids, bright Ian and bratty Claire, to settle the inheritance. Ian discovers great-grandpa's house is really haunted, and not just, as legend holds, by historic owner Zachariah Kull, who was burned on the stake.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7yNkp4WVF2gRS5jw0YXU4NWagXM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t8wEJ8SYPWQeZs8c0tnNzx3Nv1j.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Men in Black[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0119654</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Men in Black</title>
	<year>1997</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After a police chase with an otherworldly being, a New York City cop is recruited as an agent in a top-secret organization established to monitor and police alien activity on Earth: the Men in Black. Agent Kay and new recruit Agent Jay find themselves in the middle of a deadly plot by an intergalactic terrorist who has arrived on Earth to assassinate two ambassadors from opposing galaxies.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uLOmOF5IzWoyrgIF5MfUnh5pa1X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1GJvBE7UWU1WOVi0XREl4JQc7f8.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Maleficent[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1587310</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Maleficent</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A beautiful, pure-hearted young woman, Maleficent has an idyllic life growing up in a peaceable forest kingdom, until one day when an invading army threatens the harmony of the land.  Maleficent rises to be the land's fiercest protector, but she ultimately suffers a ruthless betrayal – an act that begins to turn her heart into stone. Bent on revenge, Maleficent faces an epic battle with the invading King's successor and, as a result, places a curse upon his newborn infant Aurora. As the child grows, Maleficent realizes that Aurora holds the key to peace in the kingdom – and to Maleficent's true happiness as well.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ik8PugpL41s137RAWEGTAWu0dPo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xjotE7aFdZ0D8aGriYjFOtDayct.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Maleficent: Mistress of Evil[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4777008</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Maleficent: Mistress of Evil</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Maleficent and her goddaughter Aurora begin to question the complex family ties that bind them as they are pulled in different directions by impending nuptials, unexpected allies, and dark new forces at play.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vloNTScJ3w7jwNwtNGoG8DbTThv.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/skvI4rYFrKXS73BJxWGH54Omlvv.jpg</fanart>
</item>


<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0339291</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Three wealthy children's parents are killed in a fire. When they are sent to a distant relative, they find out that he is plotting to kill them and seize their fortune.  This movie is extremely alarming, an expression which here means "a thrilling misadventure involving three ingenious orphans and a villainous actor named Count Olaf (Jim Carrey) who wants their enormous fortune."  It includes a suspicious fire, delicious pasta, Jim Carrey, poorly behaved looches, Billy Connolly, an incredibly deadly viper, Meryl Streep, and the voice of an imposter named Jude Law.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/syuIptWCGH1AlJ8AB7ZGwckHSi1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rOUj4BXAoFqhg3kWhQOAaTa5IBh.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3183660</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In 1926, Newt Scamander arrives at the Magical Congress of the United States of America with a magically expanded briefcase, which houses a number of dangerous creatures and their habitats. When the creatures escape from the briefcase, it sends the American wizarding authorities after Newt, and threatens to strain even further the state of magical and non-magical relations.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h6NYfVUyM6CDURtZSnBpz647Ldd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GrpqAs0oDcFcwFwyygnUI7BrZA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4123430</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Gellert Grindelwald has escaped imprisonment and has begun gathering followers to his cause—elevating wizards above all non-magical beings. The only one capable of putting a stop to him is the wizard he once called his closest friend, Albus Dumbledore. However, Dumbledore will need to seek help from the wizard who had thwarted Grindelwald once before, his former student Newt Scamander, who agrees to help, unaware of the dangers that lie ahead. Lines are drawn as love and loyalty are tested, even among the truest friends and family, in an increasingly divided wizarding world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fMMrl8fD9gRCFJvsx0SuFwkEOop.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qrtRKRzoNkf5vemO9tJ2Y4DrHxQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0241527</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Harry Potter has lived under the stairs at his aunt and uncle's house his whole life. But on his 11th birthday, he learns he's a powerful wizard -- with a place waiting for him at the Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. As he learns to harness his newfound powers with the help of the school's kindly headmaster, Harry uncovers the truth about his parents' deaths -- and about the villain who's to blame.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wuMc08IPKEatf9rnMNXvIDxqP4W.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4GlSMUpzSd3cliYGFJVziSDX53S.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1935859</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A teenager finds himself transported to an island where he must help protect a group of orphans with special powers from creatures intent on destroying them.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tzYkC0vqX8Dokuwynhz1lnWWgWT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ld7V9BjMk2xtiBNcR8savyyk5ca.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Spiderwick Chronicles[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0416236</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Spiderwick Chronicles</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Upon moving into the run-down Spiderwick Estate with their mother, twin brothers Jared and Simon Grace, along with their sister Mallory, find themselves pulled into an alternate world full of faeries and other creatures.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uN7MUMaCXfa8DbMMp61A8iXEcEG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uYR6VRtrTE5WU2t4mDs85NVaLpu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The House with a Clock in Its Walls[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2119543</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The House with a Clock in Its Walls</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When ten-year-old Lewis is suddenly orphaned, he is sent to live with his Uncle Jonathan in a creaky (and creepy) old mansion with a mysterious ticking noise that emanates from the walls. Upon discovering that his uncle is a warlock, Lewis begins learning magic, but when he rebelliously resurrects an evil warlock he must find the secret of the house and save the world from destruction.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qM66Hv4ByAxnilr0jaqCA9uOD4Y.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/LC9g7oNJc3jZNXUU8CkwSzVK2w.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Brothers Grimm[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0355295</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Brothers Grimm</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Folklore collectors and con artists, Jake and Will Grimm, travel from village to village pretending to protect townsfolk from enchanted creatures and performing exorcisms. However, they are put to the test  when they encounter a real magical curse in a haunted forest with real magical beings, requiring genuine courage.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v6J7QGCSrtvwvqAt6783BbO3h61.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/o9F7JsMpY8aENk5J9D2K66TwV8u.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Watcher in the Woods[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6266306</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Watcher in the Woods</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mrs. Aylwood is a distraught mother since her daughter, Karen, vanished in the English countryside over 20 years ago. When the Carstairs family move into the Aylwood manor for the summer, strange occurrences begin to unnerve the family and Jan begins to suspect that they are linked to Karen's disappearance. As Jan unravels the dark past hidden by the townspeople, she delves further into the mystery and deeper into danger, but now it might be too late to escape the Watcher in the Woods.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gWvPRXdcgfPlY7Ho7lDal5sCTqL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/knRoE689y2Kl6y5S9i62O6jmuZj.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Hocus Pocus[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107120</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hocus Pocus</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After 300 years of slumber, three sister witches are accidentally resurrected in Salem on Halloween night, and it is up to three kids and their newfound feline friend to put an end to the witches' reign of terror once and for all.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/by4D4Q9NlUjFSEUA1yrxq6ksXmk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8g2qOF0ASlXJgr1aBEU84tee2Jg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Beetlejuice[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0094721</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Beetlejuice</title>
	<year>1988</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Thanks to an untimely demise via drowning, a young couple end up as poltergeists in their New England farmhouse, where they fail to meet the challenge of scaring away the insufferable new owners, who want to make drastic changes. In desperation, the undead newlyweds turn to an expert frightmeister, but he's got a diabolical agenda of his own.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nnl6OWkyPpuMm595hmAxNW3rZFn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/su7GvFVUV5uWtAPGAVRkpDrA6Wl.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Goonies[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0089218</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Goonies</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A young teenager named Mikey Walsh finds an old treasure map in his father's attic. Hoping to save their homes from demolition, Mikey and his friends Data Wang, Chunk Cohen, and Mouth Devereaux run off on a big quest to find the secret stash of Pirate One-Eyed Willie.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/oxz1HIdUjQN23IZQk4Gy7ozJBM0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r0p9IeVzVP4OULWWw0UsDSCWtKb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Ghostbusters[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0087332</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ghostbusters</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After losing their academic posts at a prestigious university, a team of parapsychologists goes into business as proton-pack-toting "ghostbusters" who exterminate ghouls, hobgoblins and supernatural pests of all stripes. An ad campaign pays off when a knockout cellist hires the squad to purge her swanky digs of demons that appear to be living in her refrigerator.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h5Qz8J4T8YQnbZzHXM73WVYYVPK.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c6yfABGVKuB5cjoOwdX4AJMlzUz.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Ghostbusters II[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0097428</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ghostbusters II</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Five years after they defeated Gozer, the Ghostbusters are out of business. When Dana begins to have ghost problems again, the boys come out of retirement to aid her and hopefully save New York City from a new paranormal threat.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yObYPMA58DnTMvJooFW7GG6jWAt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/Ae4j8Y6EnjtPJxnIVmLMzcARZ7T.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Gremlins[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0087363</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Gremlins</title>
	<year>1984</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Billy Peltzer is given a strange but adorable pet named Gizmo for Christmas, he inadvertently breaks the three important rules of caring for a Mogwai, and unleashes a horde of mischievous gremlins on a small town.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/72Y1X9pMSjXQ7mKB6pBEoMhL0OQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6dD1pTDvFJDORvNWaIjs9BIV2JH.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083866</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After a gentle alien becomes stranded on Earth, the being is discovered and befriended by a young boy named Elliott. Bringing the extraterrestrial into his suburban California house, Elliott introduces E.T., as the alien is dubbed, to his brother and his little sister, Gertie, and the children decide to keep its existence a secret. Soon, however, E.T. falls ill, resulting in government intervention and a dire situation for both Elliott and the alien.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pEKStszBzTZCvR0H4tosjqxmE7X.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mXLVA0YL6tcXi6SJSuAh9ONXFj5.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Addams Family[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0101272</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Addams Family</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When an evil doctor finds out Uncle Fester has been missing for 25 years, he introduces a fake Fester in an attempt to get the Addams family's money. Wednesday has some doubts about the new uncle Fester, but the fake uncle adapts very well to the strange family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qFf8anju5f2epI0my8RdwwIXFIP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c49rFrkHc6P7eQYrE6irZhaWIxy.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Addams Family Values[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0106220</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Addams Family Values</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Siblings Wednesday and Pugsley Addams will stop at nothing to get rid of Pubert, the new baby boy adored by parents Gomez and Morticia. Things go from bad to worse when the new "black widow" nanny, Debbie Jellinsky, launches her plan to add Fester to her collection of dead husbands.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8znyj20O3EYLD2EzWnZQMnkE4zH.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yrjFk8OVnwOQ5qUxbHZJYobxQra.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Addams Family[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1620981</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Addams Family</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Addams family's lives begin to unravel when they face-off against a treacherous, greedy crafty reality-TV host while also preparing for their extended family to arrive for a major celebration.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/q1epO0eO8DWu8Vo8tPfvVlzW48T.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ur4NTeFGZmQ6Hz5uEkAMgPI3WRg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Scooby-Doo[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0267913</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scooby-Doo</title>
	<year>2002</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Mystery Inc. gang have gone their separate ways and have been apart for two years, until they each receive an invitation to Spooky Island. Not knowing that the others have also been invited, they show up and discover an amusement park that affects young visitors in very strange ways.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/98zsG0FX7z6R4i5q0HONLM21dpt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/70Y5eqstTp93sF2ivb3mkEqLCEi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Scooby-Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0331632</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scooby-Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Mystery, Inc. are guests of honor at the grand opening of the Coolsville Museum of Criminology, a masked villain shows up and creates havoc before stealing the costumes of the gang's most notorious villains...Could it be that their nemesis, mad scientist Jonathan Jacobo has returned and is trying to recreate their deadliest foes?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5BrXCJrs22bR5KR6mLHluYo6y4m.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hxt1WzpSqMMDVtjafAXAnMIb0o9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Scooby-Doo on Zombie Island[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0166792</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scooby-Doo on Zombie Island</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Mystery Gang reunite and visit Moonscar Island, a remote island with a dark secret. Daphne wants more than just a villain in a costume, and they get more than they ever expected.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y9CySYOtHl8mDu0GQ2eT2EcjFE9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/woFsToiI9otSnanKfChq5VKsgFp.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Goosebumps[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1051904</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Goosebumps</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After moving to a small town, Zach Cooper finds a silver lining when he meets next door neighbor Hannah, the daughter of bestselling Goosebumps series author R.L. Stine. When Zach unintentionally unleashes real monsters from their manuscripts and they begin to terrorize the town, it’s suddenly up to Stine, Zach and Hannah to get all of them back in the books where they belong.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aeZT9pqEgrmXOGdESFkAuVjX6kw.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/6mPe4rBHzDMal2oL6hVgOBkaHz9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Goosebumps 2: Haunted Halloween[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5664636</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Goosebumps 2: Haunted Halloween</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Two boys face an onslaught from witches, monsters, ghouls and a talking dummy after they discover a mysterious book by author R. L. Stine.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t2wy38iiMpB8WsgJi3lYeDnGh2H.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/h5BvesqaxL7V3vl1CmaR8waGyiM.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Mostly Ghostly[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1052024</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mostly Ghostly</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Based on the successful book series by R.L. Stine, this spooky tale finds 11-year-old Max making a deal with the ghosts who haunt his home. If Max helps them find what was responsible for their parents' disappearance, they'll help him transform from a social nobody to the most popular kid in school.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8wLYv3u9Gg1iF2CAX79nkMBFM71.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/originalNone</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Mostly Ghostly: Have You Met My Ghoulfriend?[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3138192</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mostly Ghostly: Have You Met My Ghoulfriend?</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Bella Thorne, Madison Pettis and Ryan Ochoa lead an ensemble cast in this spook-tacular adventure with new ghosts, new thrills, and the return of some old friends. Max (Ochoa) only has eyes for Cammy (Thorne), the smart, popular redhead at school. When Max finally scores a date with Cammy on Halloween, Phears, an evil ghost with plans on taking over the world, unleashes his ghouls and things go haywire. With the help of his ghostly pals, Tara and Nicky, can Max thwart Phears' evil plot, help reunite his ghost friends with their long-lost parents and still make his date with Cammy on Halloween? R.L. Stine's Mostly Ghostly: Have You Met My Ghoulfriend? is a frightful family delight!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eiVY4kKpbo1f7wyNubgJX5ILpxg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/w04mJW2N44IkplYtEAdnmW2EDvF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Mostly Ghostly 3: One Night in Doom House[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5127214</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mostly Ghostly 3: One Night in Doom House</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Just one enchanted jewel stands between earth and an army of evil spirits led by the devious ghoul, Phears. With the help of his new girlfriend and ghost pals, Max Doyle races to find the crystal and save the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dFJGCz8OvyC0U2bldruBH8OJrp6.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7IOWrwIRzg0sdq82i0NpPDu6ei.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Spooky Stakeout[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5729066</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spooky Stakeout</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Four young friends are hired to solve the particularly vexing mystery of an ancient haunted castle. Having cut their teeth on previous cases - an abandoned school building and a derelict hotel - "Team Spooky" is surprised to find a common thread behind all three mysteries. Each of the friends is driven by different motivations - whether it's for science, romance or monetary gain - but finding the real ghost is their ultimate goal!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://i.imgur.com/H1WlI7R.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/originalNone</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Halloweentown[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0173886</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Halloweentown</title>
	<year>1998</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>On her 13th birthday, Marnie learns she's a witch, discovers a secret portal, and is transported to Halloweentown — a magical place where ghosts and ghouls, witches and werewolves live apart from the human world. But she soon finds herself battling wicked warlocks, evil curses, and endless surprises.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2KLel13fLyOqN6NCP9N2JO8rbGn.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c3E5bSd4lwG4QliKTUDx18GAaAE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Halloweentown II: Kalabar's Revenge[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0274761</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Halloweentown II: Kalabar's Revenge</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Cromwell clan live in the real world, except for their grandmother who lives in Halloweentown, a place where monsters go to escape reality. But now the son of the Cromwells' old enemy Kalabar has a plan to use the grandmother's book to turn Halloweentown into a grey dreary version of the real world, while transform the denizens of the real world into monsters.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/g94VrkZ79xXp8x1XH84AZfMKyaR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xnrlLluVd7eaUUFrjfa0os4znmT.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Halloweentown High[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0414078</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Halloweentown High</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Marnie Piper prepares to begin a new school year, she asks the Halloweentown Hot Witches' Council to work toward openness between Halloweentown and the mortal world. She proposes to bring a group of Halloweentown students to her own high school in the mortal world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/rAF4CNoZyyemjyYErgnSpHs3WBa.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8yIBm3FmL0uADVnttvzRBSXaxJe.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Return to Halloweentown[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0816520</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Return to Halloweentown</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>As Halloweentown prepares to celebrate its 1,000th anniversary, Marnie Piper and her brother Dylan return to Witch University, where trouble is in session from the Sinister Sisters and from someone who's plotting to use Marnie's powers for evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yYIVsEUyGdp8bEtRjOZGwQA3qmq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zvVWINS0Nscc9qMtiry2pswhSjP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Twitches[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0467421</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Twitches</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Twins separated at birth, Camryn and Alex meet by chance for the first time on their 21st birthday and discover they're witches with the power to save their homeland of Coventry from the evil that threatens it. But when Camryn leaves Alex to face the darkness alone, will Coventry be doomed? Or will the sisters multiply their magic by standing together?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GItmNobjbF6WRATwNu2t6K9tG5.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7wJom7fFUisQGcifx8y9qSRX3l2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Twitches Too[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1017465</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Twitches Too</title>
	<year>2007</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Reunited witch twins Camryn and Alex adjust to their new life as supernatural beings while at the same time trying to maintain a normal existence in this sequel to the magical Disney Channel original movie Twitches. But they soon find themselves going head to head with the forces of darkness that threaten to destroy their world. Luckily, their birth mother, the powerful Miranda, is on hand to help out.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/70aurzbqFMuJnwhIVW2aXeyzBAp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tNKiOdq4TyVoeOhQPk39McqOHF1.jpg</fanart>
</item>




<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]A Monster Calls[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3416532</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>A Monster Calls</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A boy imagines a monster that helps him deal with his difficult life and see the world in a different way.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eNTalDnE6AcFKghdvws2ckguYWC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sBtLpesSh0pniKHGWZjgyxmtIks.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Colossal[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt4680182</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Colossal</title>
	<year>2016</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A woman discovers that severe catastrophic events are somehow connected to the mental breakdown from which she's suffering.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4VOyofBd1pexblxtDZYtYIk7NI4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aQUsuDDHofPco5YgXxEdObyisCs.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Trollhunter[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1740707</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Trollhunter</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A group of students investigates a series of mysterious bear killings, but learns that there are much more dangerous things going on. They start to follow a mysterious hunter, learning that he is actually a troll hunter.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nOcraOkfK5lGmi6jba06iB6uJNd.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gXXQEo0R54DCKczaLaByyf0Q8HF.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Where the Wild Things Are[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0386117</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Where the Wild Things Are</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Max imagines running away from his mom and sailing to a far-off land where large talking beasts -- Ira, Carol, Douglas, the Bull, Judith and Alexander -- crown him as their king, play rumpus, build forts and discover secret hideaways.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sDFV9VEjwTUWF1s5sjOllsb70jk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e0MwhnT6ydLrgQbq4IIABhJdsmo.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Edward Scissorhands[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0099487</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Edward Scissorhands</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A small suburban town receives a visit from a castaway unfinished science experiment named Edward.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1RFIbuW9Z3eN9Oxw2KaQG5DfLmD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3Nn5BOM1EVw1IYrv6MsbOS6N1Ol.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The 'Burbs[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0096734</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The 'Burbs</title>
	<year>1989</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When secretive new neighbors move in next door, suburbanite Ray Peterson and his friends let their paranoia get the best of them as they start to suspect the newcomers of evildoings and commence an investigation. But it's hardly how Ray, who much prefers drinking beer, reading his newspaper and watching a ball game on the tube expected to spend his vacation.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/AukWel2vjdmt6c5YyJ3MP0nicCC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4HJN6dyyPMJTimMglfEdVxjW2p5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Death Becomes Her[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0104070</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Death Becomes Her</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Madeline is married to Ernest, who was once arch-rival Helen's fiance. After recovering from a mental breakdown, Helen vows to kill Madeline and steal back Ernest. Unfortunately for everyone, the introduction of a magic potion causes things to be a great deal more complicated than a mere murder plot.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/vWcXU9J2RxyHN9qRXW3GDhG40t3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8vdJJjtbaPnfAgqyvLtFwlCSNdi.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]So I Married an Axe Murderer[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0108174</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>So I Married an Axe Murderer</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A San Francisco poet who fears commitment suspects his girlfriend may have a knack for killing off her significant others.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wMr6ZjfOnCHOA9Qm3jvo0e7nzfx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/A0fUbS4h62irZn8XjuPHRCa73WP.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Witches[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0100944</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Witches</title>
	<year>1990</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A young boy named Luke and his grandmother go on vacation only to discover their hotel is hosting an international witch convention, where the Grand High Witch is unveiling her master plan to turn all children into mice. Will Luke fall victim to the witches' plot before he can stop them?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/x9sHu20my4WCEqqkuVTxTHzGXSs.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/u8GO1SyKB1QBK7RON7eFhrdy9uX.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Worst Witch[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0092239</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Worst Witch</title>
	<year>1986</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mildred is one of the young girls at a prestigious witch academy. She can't seem to do anything right and is picked on by classmates and teachers. The headmistress of the school, Miss Cackle, has an evil twin sister (Agatha) who plans to destroy the school. Can Mildred foil the plan before the Grand Wizard (Tim Curry) comes to the Academy for the Halloween celebration you'll never forget?!!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/s7SmEmsttLWZCuJkvUuqEHfVotD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/69pqeCavKPSlCR5NSSdBG2CYVOr.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Something Wicked This Way Comes[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086336</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Something Wicked This Way Comes</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In a small American town, a diabolical circus arrives, granting wishes for the townsfolk, but twisted as only the esteemed Mr. Dark can make them. Can two young boys overcome the worst the devil himself can deal out?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bMGTTuwqSkaEZk38WoQm7u4mcwz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yCoyqFx0CB6Usa8xom9fU7sc44P.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Dark Crystal[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0083791</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Dark Crystal</title>
	<year>1982</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>On another planet in the distant past, a Gelfling embarks on a quest to find the missing shard of a magical crystal and restore order to his world, before the grotesque race of Skeksis find and use the crystal for evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fZPxRaa6gvCyGCh9Xk5kyPqz7fp.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ayAJltbsnde8afEDtvK3fXVeAAn.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Teen Wolf[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0090142</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Teen Wolf</title>
	<year>1985</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When a shy teenager's new-found powers help him score at basketball - and with the popular girls - he has some pretty hairy decisions to make.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bv9rY9eoue2Hat6tcvrKVQ0ow8v.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gcuqUyX0pVo0U05b8cIEG4AFeux.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Mars Attacks![/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0116996</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mars Attacks!</title>
	<year>1996</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>'We come in peace' is not what those green men from Mars mean when they invade our planet, armed with irresistible weapons and a cruel sense of humor.  This star studded cast must play victim to the alien’s fun and games in this comedy homage to science fiction films of the '50s and '60s.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hll4O5vSAfnZDb6JbnP06GPtz7b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/4qFcUKlkcUj9V9Cbh1tyyLmg2rE.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Twilight Zone: The Movie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0086491</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Twilight Zone: The Movie</title>
	<year>1983</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>This remake of four episodes of the popular television series 'The Twilight Zone. Each is very true to its original, where eerie and disturbing situations gradually spin out of control. The film consists of four chapters: 'Time Out' (directed by John Landis), 'Kick the Can' (Steven Spielberg), 'It's a Good Life' (Joe Dante), and 'Nightmare at 20,000 Feet' (George Miller).</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sn9YU2cimjf7K6tP7XvoleVux0x.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3BJrOFdbFiZJYSqMsm1kI6A0hQj.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Hellboy[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0167190</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hellboy</title>
	<year>2004</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the final days of World War II, the Nazis attempt to use black magic to aid their dying cause. The Allies raid the camp where the ceremony is taking place, but not before a demon—Hellboy—has already been conjured. Joining the Allied forces, Hellboy eventually grows to adulthood, serving the cause of good rather than evil.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pg6tCxOuON9vUqtoj8GJw1saklz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v6ejJREqtrKoveHhX7q0mwP9iUd.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Hellboy II: The Golden Army[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0411477</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hellboy II: The Golden Army</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>An evil elf breaks an ancient pact between humans and creatures, and is on a mission to release 'The Golden Army', a deadly group of fighting machines that can destroy the human race. As Hell on Earth is ready to erupt, Hellboy and his crew set out to defeat prince and his army.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/fGQAO4RgUzspO7L4u5KXirIn34s.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c1PkxFxNdGhesu6hljDiK2zcF6c.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Hellboy[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2274648</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hellboy</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Hellboy comes to England, where he must defeat Nimue, Merlin's consort and the Blood Queen. But their battle will bring about the end of the world, a fate he desperately tries to turn away.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/bk8LyaMqUtaQ9hUShuvFznQYQKR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hMbP23EkGk6tjEjRZQXhnVAl5fW.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Mummy[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0120616</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Mummy</title>
	<year>1999</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Dashing legionnaire Rick O'Connell stumbles upon the hidden ruins of Hamunaptra while in the midst of a battle to claim the area in 1920s Egypt. It has been over three thousand years since former High Priest Imhotep suffered a fate worse than death as a punishment for a forbidden love—along with a curse that guarantees eternal doom upon the world if he is ever awoken.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yhIsVvcUm7QxzLfT6HW2wLf5ajY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pwOVw2PEHwqypHbhBJFQe158Ljb.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Mummy Returns[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0209163</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Mummy Returns</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Rick and Evelyn O’Connell, along with their 8-year-old son Alex, discover the key to the legendary Scorpion King’s might: the fabled Bracelet of Anubis. Unfortunately, a newly resurrected Imhotep has designs on the bracelet as well, and isn’t above kidnapping its new bearer, Alex, to gain control of Anubis’s otherworldly army.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kdJsW7hcy1lrj7tdMPycTAQPAiR.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/uoOD6qqz4QFhgvhdsrrQUmkmAMc.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt3387520</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark</title>
	<year>2019</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Mill Valley, Pennsylvania, Halloween night, 1968. After playing a joke on a school bully, Sarah and her friends decide to sneak into a supposedly haunted house that once belonged to the powerful Bellows family, unleashing dark forces that they will be unable to control.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/n7GvmHR10Rr4L17pX5fiErjarNf.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/snll1zUi2oxIah9qifXOvbfjcrG.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Summer of 84[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt5774450</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Summer of 84</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Summer is usually a time for fun and games, but some teens get much more danger than they bargained for after beginning to suspect their neighbor is a serial murderer.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/qPitgXPCIFh23yCEjqnCZnfhBig.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iEYDBciiuW68Q5bLCzkVBgKnfi7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Hole[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1085779</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Hole</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>After moving into a new neighbourhood, brothers Dane &amp; Lucas and their neighbour Julie discover a bottomless hole in the basement of their home. They find that once the hole is exposed, evil is unleashed. With strange shadows lurking around every corner and nightmares coming to life, they are forced to come face to face with their darkest fears to put an end to the mystery of THE HOLE.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/tQMxsrsVtpB2D2n01nUqgOMmSWD.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/xQtdBzy67er6alpexwalnuihrOu.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Dracula Untold[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0829150</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Dracula Untold</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Vlad Tepes is a great hero, but when he learns the Sultan is preparing for battle and needs to form an army of 1,000 boys, he vows to find a way to protect his family. Vlad turns to dark forces in order to get the power to destroy his enemies and agrees to go from hero to monster as he's turned into the mythological vampire, Dracula.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7tVWoOYLPHBwE0TFUK48BZAXzyJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/f02FFv77Rh62633YEjimv7C6JM3.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Twilight[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1099212</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Twilight</title>
	<year>2008</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Bella Swan moves to a small town in the Pacific Northwest to live with her father, she meets the reclusive Edward Cullen, a mysterious classmate who reveals himself to be a 108-year-old vampire. Despite Edward's repeated cautions, Bella can't help but fall in love with him, a fatal move that endangers her own life when a coven of bloodsuckers try to challenge the Cullen clan.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/3Gkb6jm6962ADUPaCBqzz9CTbn9.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7eK8FJr4fqq3J5W2xvlr2GVaep2.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Twilight Saga: New Moon[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1259571</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Twilight Saga: New Moon</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Forks, Washington resident Bella Swan is reeling from the departure of her vampire love, Edward Cullen, and finds comfort in her friendship with Jacob Black, a werewolf. But before she knows it, she's thrust into a centuries-old conflict, and her desire to be with Edward at any cost leads her to take greater and greater risks.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/j5jM5pq78ObAXX1WhTsb115EkLl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/eWAmfnP2DGIS2sEZ8tSua6yfwLA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Twilight Saga: Eclipse[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1325004</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Twilight Saga: Eclipse</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Bella once again finds herself surrounded by danger as Seattle is ravaged by a string of mysterious killings and a malicious vampire continues her quest for revenge. In the midst of it all, she is forced to choose between her love for Edward and her friendship with Jacob, knowing that her decision has the potential to ignite the ageless struggle between vampire and werewolf. With her graduation quickly approaching, Bella is confronted with the most important decision of her life.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sOpCY4by0bkEu9LbVXVCOpWWKzF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yiWfT2Bl1Nul3Xie39Ahs3FqSjA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Buffy the Vampire Slayer[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0103893</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Buffy the Vampire Slayer</title>
	<year>1992</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Blonde, bouncy Buffy is your typical high school cheerleader: her goal is to "marry Christian Slater and die," and nothing gets in her way when it's time to shop! But all that changes when a strange man informs her she's been chosen by fate to kill vampires.  With the help of a romantic rebel, Buffy is soon spending school nights protecting L.A. from Lothos the Vampire King, his sidekick, Lefty, and their determined gang of bloodsuckers. It's everything you'd expect from a teen queen in the Valley.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/so4tTMItoq90wphs18lWbV0ASVV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/v9BNwCSm67p90O2BbukcsjDclP9.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Ernest Scared Stupid[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0101821</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Ernest Scared Stupid</title>
	<year>1991</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Well-intentioned, eternally bumbling Ernest P. Worrell accidentally releases an evil demon from its sacred tomb. As the demon flexes its power and goes on a ruinous rampage, good-guy Ernest tries to step in to save the town from mass destruction. Trouble is, a 200-year-old curse has scared Ernest stupid, and that means hilarity all around! So, kick back and let the laugh-ridden adventures begin.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dISQ2ltIzCkCYNJt20PgB1zOchT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aGKaNn1odcBR2zecCvPIcr7RzP1.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Super Monsters Save Halloween[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt9085726</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Super Monsters Save Halloween</title>
	<year>2018</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>It's Halloween in Pitchfork Pines, but the neighbors don't seem to be in the mood. Can the Super Monsters save their favorite holiday?</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c23CDexw6JJLAIAUf0evS2VahCx.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/y4ZyK00aVmq7hmKxZQcTNz7IVRg.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Spooky Buddies[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1792131</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spooky Buddies</title>
	<year>2011</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Disney's irresistible talking puppies are back in an all-new movie that takes them far across town to a mysterious mansion where something very spooky is going on.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iPXai8I7jnEZ4vbNLryV8K8bIOC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/1c5qE7EVz3OYVWC0bADlKnNQD2V.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Happy Family[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt6572702</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Happy Family</title>
	<year>2017</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>The Wishbone family is far from happy. With a struggling bookshop, an overworked husband, and two misunderstood teenagers, Emma is at her wit's end trying to be the perfect mom. After dragging her family to a costume party on Halloween night, they are cursed by an evil witch and transformed into a Vampire, a Mummy, a Werewolf, and Frankenstein's monster. Now Emma will fight to keep her Monster Family together and uncover the secret of their curse... eventually leading them to the Prince of Darkness himself, Dracula!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r3xY0tCI05iUmm8M7fAkKtqGPXM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/t5ZTLzn0ASdOhY3S8o3vzj57Myg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Casper[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0112642</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Casper</title>
	<year>1995</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Furious that her late father only willed her his gloomy-looking mansion rather than his millions, Carrigan Crittenden is ready to burn the place to the ground when she discovers a map to a treasure hidden in the house. But when she enters the rickety mansion to seek her claim, she is frightened away by a wicked wave of ghosts. Determined to get her hands on this hidden fortune, she hires afterlife therapist Dr. James Harvey to exorcise the ghosts from the mansion. Harvey and his daughter Kat move in, and soon Kat meets Casper, the ghost of a young boy who's "the friendliest ghost you know." But not so friendly are Casper's uncles--Stretch, Fatso and Stinkie--who are determined to drive all "fleshies" away.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2ah8fNJFZVU3vcXhU5xfAYi2eym.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yDjTmd4Wgq7qkXBAobjHyfeyYZg.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Monster House[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0385880</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Monster House</title>
	<year>2006</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Monsters under the bed are scary enough, but what happens when an entire house is out to get you? Three teens aim to find out when they go up against a decrepit neighboring home and unlock its frightening secrets.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zCRPr4bkO3ae0U1134vJ39xZnAG.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aiRESjcG3Vi3W9WAGgMJSjGX1HQ.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]ParaNorman[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1623288</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>ParaNorman</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>In the town of Blithe Hollow, Norman Babcock can speak to the dead, but no one other than his eccentric new friend believes his ability is real. One day, Norman's eccentric uncle tells him of a ritual he must perform to protect the town from a curse cast by a witch centuries ago.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9DZPtuYTKYxt6vzHvZ5FLThG4fl.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7GPemb4DkuxlicKiQP5V5f2Wwtg.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Frankenweenie[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1142977</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Frankenweenie</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When a car hits young Victor's pet dog Sparky, Victor decides to bring him back to life the only way he knows how. But when the bolt-necked "monster" wreaks havoc and terror in the hearts of Victor's neighbors, he has to convince them that Sparky's still the good, loyal friend he was.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/yGjVbLVdZRBlZTTQVBsj2KUjL1s.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/zu8QKHnL9a3bI82p8wTEmvvd5QC.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Toy Story of Terror![/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2446040</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Toy Story of Terror!</title>
	<year>2013</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>What starts out as a fun road trip for the Toy Story gang takes an unexpected turn for the worse when the trip detours to a roadside motel. After one of the toys goes missing, the others find themselves caught up in a mysterious sequence of events that must be solved before they all suffer the same fate in this Toy Story of Terror.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aNDrMDZYmcoMlJa6K3VicYeAgt1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/chICYTbG39OUQHVoHP11ehIoXV7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Scared Shrekless[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt1725156</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Scared Shrekless</title>
	<year>2010</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Shrek challenges Donkey, Puss in Boots and his other fairy tale character friends to spend the night in Lord Farquaad's haunted castle, telling scary stories to see who can resist becoming scared and stay the longest.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/lb7K0VYUvJHiZ6sy7niNbtDJwj2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/9QXx4tS65s3oUBoQ27bMIwmBD9x.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Shrek's Thrilling Tales[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2486724</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Shrek's Thrilling Tales</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>SHREK'S THRILLING TALES is the ultimate Halloween DVD compilation for your family. Shrek's Thrilling Tales review Featuring the scariest, ugliest, and funniest characters from DreamWorks Animation's successful SHREK and MONSTERS VS. ALIENS franchises. DVD includes 'The Pig who Cried (Were)Wolf' and 'The Ghost of Lord Farquaad' from the Shrek movies, and 'Night of the Living Carrots' from Monsters vs. Aliens, featuring B.O.B.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/wH4zCbgNJxjnQAzJj48zitzsu3A.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/originalNone</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Hotel Transylvania[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0837562</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hotel Transylvania</title>
	<year>2012</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Welcome to Hotel Transylvania, Dracula's lavish five-stake resort, where monsters and their families can live it up and no humans are allowed. One special weekend, Dracula has invited all his best friends to celebrate his beloved daughter Mavis's 118th birthday. For Dracula catering to all of these legendary monsters is no problem but the party really starts when one ordinary guy stumbles into the hotel and changes everything!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/c8xgxYJHmIHHREFxlNqUD23kvvc.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sETTal2HPPkUC3lWc27HL1AFu9C.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Hotel Transylvania 2[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt2510894</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Hotel Transylvania 2</title>
	<year>2015</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When the old-old-old-fashioned vampire Vlad arrives at the hotel for an impromptu family get-together, Hotel Transylvania is in for a collision of supernatural old-school and modern day cool.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/kKFgwQnR5q08UFsAvtoYyTIiHyj.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aY7hLxI5DoYzxbdz2rdPK7jnJJn.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Monsters, Inc.[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0198781</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Monsters, Inc.</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>James Sullivan and Mike Wazowski are monsters, they earn their living scaring children and are the best in the business... even though they're more afraid of the children than they are of them. When a child accidentally enters their world, James and Mike suddenly find that kids are not to be afraid of and they uncover a conspiracy that could threaten all children across the world.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/sgheSKxZkttIe8ONsf2sWXPgip3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/pGK0oaeIVxpIroNHu1wDqXf4vv5.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Monsters vs Aliens[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0892782</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Monsters vs Aliens</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Susan Murphy is unwittingly clobbered by a meteor full of outer space gunk on her wedding day, she mysteriously grows to 49-feet-11-inches. The military jumps into action and captures Susan, secreting her away to a covert government compound. She is renamed Ginormica and placed in confinement with a ragtag group of Monsters...</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/iVei1uT1IkbKcM2JRca9KEoTRXM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gUIyXIjQIFlmeXVcmVDAaKhhk04.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Corpse Bride[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0121164</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Corpse Bride</title>
	<year>2005</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Set in a 19th-century european village, this stop-motion animation feature follows the story of Victor, a young man whisked away to the underworld and wed to a mysterious corpse bride, while his real bride Victoria waits bereft in the land of the living.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/isb2Qow76GpqYmsSyfdMfsYAjts.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/r4VumNLSafeGhlieKNhGv0BQ4UD.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Coraline[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0327597</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Coraline</title>
	<year>2009</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Coraline moves to an old house, she feels bored and neglected by her parents. She finds a hidden door with a bricked up passage. During the night, she crosses the passage and finds a parallel world where everybody has buttons instead of eyes, with caring parents and all her dreams coming true. When the Other Mother invites Coraline to stay in her world forever, the girl refuses and finds that the alternate reality where she is trapped is only a trick to lure her.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ytBaJAcaTvONnOBziIijzkMk64f.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/8GHxjXlI5rqyTBuVNekGTPjG5T6.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Nightmare Before Christmas[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0107688</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Nightmare Before Christmas</title>
	<year>1993</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>Tired of scaring humans every October 31 with the same old bag of tricks, Jack Skellington, the spindly king of Halloween Town, kidnaps Santa Claus and plans to deliver shrunken heads and other ghoulish gifts to children on Christmas morning. But as Christmas approaches, Jack's rag-doll girlfriend, Sally, tries to foil his misguided plans.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e4pZZR1SZByveyWczQBmiXJ0lXP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/16lk65YfrDFIr6evkWRjSeOOSws.jpg</fanart>
</item>


<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]The Boxtrolls[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0787474</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>The Boxtrolls</title>
	<year>2014</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>An orphaned boy raised by underground creatures called Boxtrolls comes up from the sewers and out of his box to save his family and the town from the evil exterminator, Archibald Snatcher.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/GXOIM93ZrOFUtYfR2rQIxgsYUJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/dkBx0XNzsngDDqiWiPG08eMWBm7.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Spirited Away[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0245429</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Spirited Away</title>
	<year>2001</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>A young girl, Chihiro, becomes trapped in a strange new world of spirits. When her parents undergo a mysterious transformation, she must call upon the courage she never knew she had to free her family.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/2TeJfUZMGolfDdW6DKhfIWqvq8y.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/mSDsSDwaP3E7dEfUPWy4J0djt4O.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]It's the Great Pumpkin, Charlie Brown[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0060550</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>It's the Great Pumpkin, Charlie Brown</title>
	<year>1966</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>This classic "Peanuts" tale focuses on the thumb-sucking, blanket-holding Linus, and his touching faith in the "Great Pumpkin." When Linus discovers that no one else believes in the creature, he sets out to prove that the Pumpkin's no myth—by spending the night alone in a pumpkin patch.</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/aMJzL6JGAJVzoh0yVmBU0sCHLNP.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/hlcpyGNi47Gs7oJS1Cz1UigB6JA.jpg</fanart>
</item>
<item>
	<title>[COLOR=gainsboro]Mad Monster Party?[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
	<imdb>tt0061931</imdb>
	<content>movie</content>
	<title>Mad Monster Party?</title>
	<year>1967</year>
	</meta>
	<link>
	<sublink>search</sublink>
	<sublink>searchsd</sublink>
	</link>
	<summary>When Dr Frankenstein decides to retire from the monster-making business, he calls an international roster of monsters to a creepy convention to elect his successor. Everyone is there including Dracula, The Werewolf, The Creature, Dr Jekyll &amp; Mr Hyde and many more. But Frankenstein's title is not all that is at stake. The famous doctor has also discovered the secret of total destruction that must not fall into the wrong hands!</summary>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/nuaiQaZ0V2zWYKy0Q0ig4jmyN6q.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/e9DWDTkok5aAWrqVJrTEbUdiuqy.jpg</fanart>
</item>




